export const state = () => ({
  all: [
    {
      question: "What do you call a snake that's shed its skin?",
      answer: 'Naked.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call Santa at the South Pole?',
      answer: 'A lost Claus.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What side of a cat has the most fur?',
      answer: 'The outside.',
    },
    {
      question:
        'What did the buffalo say when he dropped his son off at school?',
      answer: 'Bye son.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why was the pig in the kitchen?',
      answer: 'It was bacon.',
    },
    {
      question: "Why aren't koalas actual bears?",
      answer: "They don't meet the koalafications.",
    },
    {
      question: "What's smarter than a talking parrot?",
      answer: 'A spelling bee.',
    },
    {
      question: 'How do porcupines talk to each other?',
      answer: 'With spine language.',
    },
    {
      question:
        'What do you call 2 monkeys that share an Amazon prime account?',
      answer: 'Prime mates.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What are bears without bees?',
      answer: 'Ears.',
    },
    {
      question: "Why can't you give Elsa a balloon?",
      answer: 'Because she will let it go...',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why did half a chicken cross the road?',
      answer: 'To get to his other side.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why did the skunk cross the road?',
      answer: 'To get to the odor side.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of bagel can fly?',
      answer: 'A plain bagel!',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a fake noodle?',
      answer: 'An impasta.',
    },
    {
      question:
        'How is the alphabet different on Christmas than any other day?',
      answer: 'On Christmas, it has Noel.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why did the couple get hitched on the 24th of December?',
      answer: 'So they could have a married Christmas.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the gingerbread man use to make his bed?',
      answer: 'Cookie sheets.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call an elf who has just won the lottery?',
      answer: 'Welfy.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who says "Oh Oh Oh"?',
      answer: 'Santa Claus walking backwards.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who delivers presents to baby sharks at Christmas?',
      answer: 'Santa Jaws.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a blind reindeer?',
      answer: 'I have no eye deer.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a scary-looking reindeer?',
      answer: 'A cariboo.',
    },
    {
      question: "What's the smartest type of animal at the North Pole?",
      answer: 'Brain deer.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Where do reindeer like to stop for ice cream?',
      answer: 'Deery Queen.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do snowmen eat for breakfast?',
      answer: 'Frosted Flakes or Ice Crispies.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do reindeer eat for breakfast?',
      answer: 'Deerios.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a snowman that can walk?',
      answer: 'A snow mobile.',
    },
    {
      question: "What is a Christmas tree's favorite candy?",
      answer: 'Ornamints.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why was the snowman rummaging in a bag of carrots?',
      answer: 'He was picking his nose.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why is everyone so thirsty at the North Pole?',
      answer: 'No well, no well!',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does Good King Wenceslas like his pizza?',
      answer: 'Deep pan, crisp and even!',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you get if you eat onions on your beans?',
      answer: 'Tear gas.',
    },
    {
      question: 'How much do I love tacos?',
      answer: 'From my head tomatoes.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a perfect name for a princess who loves tacos?',
      answer: 'Taco Bella.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is an ideal match for the Taco Beast?',
      answer: 'Taco Belle.',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can a taco get out of taco jail?',
      answer: 'By getting Taco Bail.',
    },
    {
      question: 'Why did the waiter give me a taco when I asked for nachos?',
      answer: 'It was just a bad queso miscommunication.',
    },
    {
      question: 'What do you call a tiny boat made out of fried corn?',
      answer: 'A tortilla ship.',
    },
    {
      question: 'How does a tortilla chip sneeze?',
      answer: '"Na-choooooo!"',
    },
    {
      question:
        ' What did one taco say to the other when he was acting unusual? ',
      answer: '"You are nachoself today."',
    },
  ],
})
